

Sr. Software Developer seeking roles in Project Management, website development, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Production Support, Unit Testing, Coding, Debugging, Application Maintenance, Core PHP, Opencart, YII2, MySql, Javascript, Jquery



Current Designation: Sr. Software Developer Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Codefire Technologies Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Noida Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Advanced Computing]

Pref. Location: Greater Noida, Noida, Delhi

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Sr. Software Developer, Project Management, website development, Software Development, Requirement

Gathering, Production Support, Unit Testing, Coding, Debugging, Application Maintenance, Core

PHP, Opencart, YII2, MySql, Javascript, Jquery

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

A result-oriented professional with over 7 years of experience in website development in PHP. Working as Sr. Software Developer in Codefire Technologies, Noida from 1st May 2017 to present. Here I am developing websites in PHP (Core PHP, YII2, Opencart) based on different projects

Work Experience

Codefire Technologies as Sr. Software Developer

May 2017 to Till Date

Here I am developing websites in PHP (Core PHP, YII2, Opencart) based on different projects.

My Recent Projects:

Adbooks:-- An e-commerce website developed in Opencart. I have developed this website from scratch. This website can be viewed at "https://adbooks.in/".

Ideateplus:-- An online platform to explore ideas for some problem from employees of a company and rate their ideas on certain parameters. This website can be viewed at https://app.ideateplus.com/.

Redhealth:-- An online healthcare platform. This website is developed in YII2. This website can be viewed at "https://redhealth.in/".

Abdos: An app to shop for medical devices. I developed its admin panel and APIs to connect with app. Its admin panel is developed in Opencart. This website can be viewed at http://www.abdoslifesciences.com/

XS Infosol Inc. as Software Developer

Dec 2014 to Apr 2017

Here I was developing and maintaining a BMS product -

Smartguard. Also I was team lead of Smartguard, Billing, OMS and Helpdesk teams.

Velocity Software Solutions Ltd as Software Engineer Nov 2013 to Nov 2014

Here I have to develop plugins for Opencart stores.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Radharaman Engineering College, Bhopal, affiliated to, Rajeev Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya in 2012

PG: PG Diploma (Advanced Computing) from Centre for Development of Advanced Computing (CDAC) in 2013

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
core php			
opencart			
Yii2			
MySQL			
JavaScript/Jquery			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time